t<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.shiftey.Desktop</id>
  <name>Github-desktop</name>
  <summary>GitHub Desktop is an open source GitHub app</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>
      GitHub Desktop is an open source GitHub app. This version of Github Desktop is a fork that adds support for Linux
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/shiftkey/desktop#readme</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.shiftey.Desktop.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
          <image>https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/359239/26094502/a1f56d02-3a5d-11e7-8799-23c7ba5e5106.png</image>
        </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1" />
  <releases>
        <release version="2.9.2" date="2020-7-14">
            <description>
            	<p>Additions</p>
            	<p>Show number of lines changed in a commit.
            	   Include owner in suggested path when cloning a repository.
            	   Added editor support for Kate and gEdit.
            	   Upgraded to Electron 11.4.11 to resolve some segfaults found when testing.
            	</p>
            	<p>Fixes</p>
                <p>
                Green circle in progress dialog remains round when commits have long descriptions.
                History tab shows all commits as the user scrolls down. 
                Remove border of Repository and Branch foldouts in dark theme.
                Render links in commit messages when they are at the beginning of a line.
                Show co-authors from undone commits.
                Show SSH prompts (key passphrase, adding host, etc.) to users via dialog.
                Change the diff gutter width based on number of lines in diff.
                Fix scrolling performance issue for large diffs.
                Check invalidated tokens and prompt the user to sign in again.
                Double-click an option when switching branches to confirm how changed files are handled.
                Improve auth error and prompt to suggest the user use a PAT instead of password.
                Increase visibility of misattributed commit warning in dark mode.
                Reduce time needed to make a commit
                </p>
            </description>
        </release>
    </releases>
</component>
