<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
  <id>io.github.shiftey.Desktop</id>
  <name>GitHub Desktop</name>
  <summary>Simple collaboration from your desktop</summary>
  <metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
  <project_license>MIT</project_license>
  <description>
    <p>
      Focus on what matters instead of fighting with Git. Whether you're new to Git or a seasoned user, GitHub Desktop simplifies your development workflow.
    </p>
    <p>
      Attribute commits with collaborators easily. Quickly add co-authors to your commit. Great for pairing and excellent for sending a little love/credit to that special someone who helped fix that gnarly bug of yours. See the attribution on the history page, undo an accidental attribution, and see the co-authors on github.com
    </p>
    <p>
      Checkout branches with pull requests and view CI statuses. See all open pull requests for your repositories and check them out as if they were a local branch, even if they're from upstream branches or forks. See which pull requests pass commit status checks, too!]
    </p>
    <p>
      Syntax highlighted diffs. The new GitHub Desktop supports syntax highlighting when viewing diffs for a variety of different languages.
    </p>
    <p>
      Expanded image diff support. Easily compare changed images. See the before and after, swipe or fade between the two, or look at just the changed parts.
    </p>
    <p>
      Extensive editor &amp; shell integrations. Open your favorite editor or shell from the app, or jump back to GitHub Desktop from your shell. GitHub Desktop is your springboard for work.
    </p>
    <p>
      Community supported. GitHub Desktop is open source now! Check out our roadmap, contribute, and help us make collaboration even easier.
    </p>
    <p>
      This version of GitHub Desktop is a fork that adds support for Linux.
    </p>
  </description>
  <url type="homepage">https://github.com/shiftkey/desktop#readme</url>
  <launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.shiftey.Desktop.desktop</launchable>
  <screenshots>
        <screenshot type="default">
          <image>https://cloud.githubusercontent.com/assets/359239/26094502/a1f56d02-3a5d-11e7-8799-23c7ba5e5106.png</image>
        </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
  <content_rating type="oars-1.1"/>
  <releases>
        <release version="3.2.7-linux2" date="2023-07-29"/>
        <release version="3.2.6-linux1" date="2023-07-04"/>
        <release version="3.2.5-linux1" date="2023-07-04"/>
        <release version="3.2.1-linux2" date="2023-04-10"/>
        <release version="3.2.0-linux1" date="2023-03-02"/>
        <release version="3.1.8-linux1" date="2023-02-27"/>
        <release version="3.1.7-linux1" date="2023-02-17"/>
        <release version="3.1.5-linux2" date="2023-01-30"/>
        <release version="3.1.1-linux1" date="2022-10-15">
          <description>
            <p>Fixes and improvements</p>
            <ul>
              <li>App correctly remembers undo commit prompt setting</li>
            </ul>
          </description>
        </release>
        <release version="3.0.7-linux1" date="2022-09-08"/>
        <release version="3.0.5-linux1" date="2022-08-03"/>
        <release version="3.0.4-linux1" date="2022-07-26"/>
        <release version="3.0.3-linux1" date="2022-07-07"/>
        <release version="3.0.2-linux1" date="2022-06-25">
            <description>
                <p>Fixes and improvements</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Updated electron from 17.4.0 to 17.4.5</li>
                </ul> 
            </description>
        </release>
    </releases> 
</component>
